Aman Khandelwal

Alwar, Rajasthan, India



aman.khandelwal1205@gmail.com



9261638242



linkedin.com/in/aman-khandelwal-1205

Summary

Hello there,

Thanks for coming here to get to know more about me.

I'm Aman Khandelwal, currently pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering. I am a Website Front End Developer and a Digital Marketer, having expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, React Native, Node Js, React Js. Moreover, I have a deep interest in Android Development as well. Other than academics, I am the Founder of a tech start-up (IT & Digital Marketing service providing company) named Flaanzo Technologies where I along with my team provide various online services which a business needs to grow.

What can I do for you?

- 1. Website Development
- 2. Responsive Website UI/UX Design
- 3. Mobile App Development
- 4. Responsive Mobile App UI/UX Designing
- 5. Graphic Designing
- 6. Promotional Video Production

Other than the website and application-based services, my company also provide marketing services as -

- 1. Complete Digital Marketing Services
- 2. SEO Search Engine Optimization
- 3. SMO Social Media Optimization
- 4. Social Media Marketing
- 5. Google Ads (PPC Campain)
- 6. Lead Generation
- 7. E-mail Marketing
- 8. SEO Content Writing/Copy Writing

To avail my services and to get more details about us you can shoot me a message or drop an E-mail under mentioned E-Mail address.

E-Mail Address - flaanzotechnologies@gmail.com

Experience



Founder

Flaanzo Technologies

May 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

Flaanzo Technologies is a start-up that has turned up in to a very successful Digital Marketing and Software Development Company. Within a very short span of 1 Year, Flaanzo Technologies has completed more than 10 successful projects, resulting in happy & long-term collaboration with our clients.

Flaanzo Technologies is well known in the market for delivering the assigned projects par above the expectations of the clients with perfection on the committed time duration. With Flaanzo Technologies, you can avail various services that includes

- 1. Website Development
- 2. Responsive Website UI/UX Design
- 3. Mobile App Development
- 4. Responsive Mobile App UI/UX Designing
- 5. Digital Marketing
- 6. SEO Search Engine Optimization
- 7. SMO Social Media Optimization
- 8. Social Media Marketing
- 9. Google Ads (PPC Campain)
- 10. Lead Generation
- 11. E-mail Marketing
- 12. SEO Content Writing/Copy Writing

To avail my services and to get more details about us you can shoot me a message or drop an E-mail under mentioned E-Mail address.

E-Mail Address - flaanzotechnologies@gmail.com

Search Engine Optimization Intern

Tractor Junction

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021 (6 months)

The work responsibilities include complete website optimization for getting a top ranking in SERP to acquire useful traffic and best conversations. In this, I'm Integrating proper competitive analysis and best SEO strategies including both On-Page and Off-Page activities.

Intermediate SEO Content Optimization Intern

Tractor Junction

Dec 2020 - Apr 2021 (5 months)

The work responsibilities include SEO friendly content planning, writing, and optimization. Majorly optimizing the website content with useful keywords to create keyword rich and SEO friendly content helps in better ranking in SERP. Other than this, writing product descriptions, guest posts, micro blogs, and articles.

Education

MITRC College, Alwar

Bachelor of Technology - B.Tech, Computer Science Engineering 2019 - 2023

I'm Aman Khandelwal, pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering. I am a Website Front End Developer, Digital Marketer, and Founder of a tech start-up (IT & Digital Marketing service providing company) named Flaanzo Technologies.

Licenses & Certifications

Google Digital Unlocked - The Fundamental of Digital Marketing - Google Digital Garage

BQKEV3HSW

Google Analytics for Beginners - Google analytics

Skills

Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Front-end Development • Google Search Console • Technical SEO • Wordpress Development • Search Engine Marketing (SEM) • Digital Marketing • Content Marketing • Web Content Writing • SEO Content Writing